[{"id": 2637, "question": "I took the bus to work for many years. No one knew each other; the passengers all sat there sleepily in the morning. The bus was cheerless and silent. One of the passengers was a small gray-haired man who took the bus to the center for senior citizens every morning. No one ever paid very much attention to him. One July morning he said good morning to the driver and smiled. The driver nodded guardedly . The rest of us were silent. The next day, the old man boarded with a big smile and said in a loud voice: \"A very good morning to you all!\" Some of us looked up, amazed, and murmured \"Good Morning\" in reply. The following weeks, our friend was dressed in a nice old suit and tie. His thin hair had been carefully combed. He said good morning to us every day and we gradually began to nod and tal...\n\nQ: Which would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How to Shorten the Distance between People", "Smiles Make a Bus Feel Like Home", "Charlie, A Smiling Gentle Man", "The Key to Friendship -- Communication"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 201, "question": "We produce 500 billion of plastic bags in a year worldwide and they are thrown away polluting oceans, killing wildlife and getting dumped in landfills where they take up to 1000 years to decompose. Researchers have been unsuccessfully looking for a solution. The 16-year old Canadian high school student, Daniel Burd, from Waterloo Collegiate Institute, has discovered a way to make plastic bags degrade in as few as 3 months, a finding that won him first prize at the Canada-Wide Science Fair, a $10 000 prize, a $20 000 scholarship, and a chance to revolutionize a major environmental issue. Burd's strategy was simple: Since plastic does eventually degrade, it must be eaten by microorganisms . If those microorganisms could be identified, we could put them to work eating the plastic much faster ...\n\nQ: Daniel Burd got his idea from   _  .", "options": ["his school textbook", "the failure of researchers", "his everyday work", "the practice of other people"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1688, "question": "Americans often say that there are only two things a person can be sure of:death and taxes.Many people feel that the United States has the worst taxes in the world. Taxes are the money that people pay to support their government.There are generally three levels of government in the United States:federal,state,and city;therefore,there are three types of taxes. Salaried people who can earn more than four to five thousand dollars per year must pay a certain part.It depends on their salaries.The federal government has a two-level income tax:that is,15 or 28 percent.$17 850 is the cut off.The tax rate is 15 percent below $17 850 and 28 percent above. The second tax is for the state government:New York,California,or any of the other forty-eight states.Some states have an income tax similar to th...\n\nQ: After reading the passage,we might feel that Americans seem to be    .", "options": ["satisfied with their taxes", "proud of their taxes", "unhappy about their taxes", "very angry at their taxes"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1564, "question": "Two things changed my life: my mother and a white plastic bike basket. I have thought long and hard about it and it's true. I would be a different person if my mom hadn't turned a silly bicycle accessory into a life lesson I carry with me today. My mother and father were united in their way of raising children, but it mostly fell to my mother to actually carry it out. Looking back, I honestly don't know how she did it. Managing the family budget must have been a very hard task., but she made it look effortless. If we complained about not having what another kid did, we'd hear something like, \"I don't care what so -and -so got for his birthday, you are not getting a TV in your room a car for your birthday a lsvish sweet 16 party.\" We had to earn our allowance by doing chores around the hous...\n\nQ: What is the life lesson the author learned from her mother?", "options": ["Save money for a rainy day", "Good advice is beyond all price.", "Earn your bread with your sweat", "God helps those who help themselves"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 249, "question": "Worn by the rich and famous around the world and now a $799.04 million-a-year enterprise , Ugg boots have come a long way since their 1973 creation--designed to keep surfers' feet warm in cold Australian conditions. Twenty-eight years after selling the rights to his woollen-lined creation, Aussie Ugg boot inventor Shane Stedman says he has no regrets though missing out on a great footwear fortune . A lifelong surfer, Mr. Stedman, now 69, who lives at beachside Mona Vale in Sydney, said his invention grew from need. \"The sea is bloody cold in the Aussie winter...I used to wear football jerseys to keep them (feet) warm\", Mr. Stedman said. But his sheepskin invention soon solved the problem and Mr. Stedman went on to spend a decade selling the sturdy boots, until 1983 when he sold the rights ...\n\nQ: When Mr. Stedman said, \"...I was happy to let go. \", he meant he was happy to   _  .", "options": ["go to the USA", "give up his boots company", "go surfing in Sydney", "buy an American company"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1630, "question": "Most people consider skydiving a product of the 20th century, but its history actually goes further back than that. The Chinese attempted to parachute in the 10th century, a thousand years before we did. The Chinese did what we would today call base diving; that is, they jumped off a place that would allow them to float from a height to the ground. The first person to attempt to parachute was a Frenchman named Jacques Garnerin. He jumped from his hot-air balloon at the end of the 18th century and did tricks on the way down and _ the crowds by landing safely on the ground. At the end of the 19th century, Kathie Paulus, a brave German woman, became famous for her skydiving skills. Once the airplane was invented, skydiving took on a whole new form. The airplane made it possible to dive from g...\n\nQ: Who was the first woman to jump from a plane?", "options": ["Jacques Garnerin.", "Kathie Paulus.", "Tiny Broadwick.", "Ronald Young."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2645, "question": "Are you a creative person? Are you looking for a challenging and unique work environment? Picture yourself at CRIENGLISH.com Positions open to native English Speakers Only Video reporters/editors: 1. Video editing experience with an understanding of Final Cut Pro software. 2. Resourceful and creative when it comes to finding original stories. 3. A comfortable demeanor in front of the camera. 4. Enjoy working with others in a team oriented environment. News presenters: 1. Journalistic and radio experience, good news-writing skills. 2. Able to work the night and early morning shifts. 3. Team spirit and flexibility. Biz News Reporter/Presenter: 1. Journalistic experience, particularly in the field of business news. 2. Good reading and presentation skills. 3. Able to work at irregular hours. C...\n\nQ: What's the purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To advertise a website.", "To attract some talents.", "To introduce a radio station.", "To introduce a company."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 833, "question": "Homesick is a compound word made up of HOME and SICK.You know what each word means on its own, of course.But think about what the words mean when they are used together.Homesick means SICK FOR HOME. Now think for a minute about SEASICK.If you change the word home in the definition to the word sea, would the definition fit SEASICK? Seasick means SICK BY THE MOVEMENT ON THE SEA. When you are homesick ,the only place you want to be is at home.When you are seasick, the last place you want to be is at seA. Have you ever heard of a person being heartsick? Heartsick doesn't mean that something is wrong with a person's heart.people are heartsick when they are hurt deep inside and when they feel as if their hearts are broken. But, on the other hand, we have such compound words as handshake, handsta...\n\nQ: When we say a person is heartsick, we mean that  _  .", "options": ["his heart is sick", "his heart needs testing", "he's sorry at heart", "he's terribly disappointed and sad,"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 196, "question": "Oliver Radtke believes Chinglish mistranslations may be fun, but are not to be made fun of. \"My message on Chinglish is: It should be conserved . It shouldn't be treated as a cheap joke for foreign tourists to laugh at but as a cultural treasure,\" said the 32-year-old multimedia designer, who frequently visited China for almost a decade before moving to Beijing in 2007. \"I'm trying to challenge the idea that there is only one type of standard English -- the English that's spoken in America or in the British Isles -- which is shortsighted, because Chinglish is already being used by millions of people to communicate with one another.\" So, since 2005, he has collected more than 5,000 examples of \"the wonderful results of an English dictionary meeting Chinese grammar\" on his website www.chingl...\n\nQ: The two books are unique because it involves the following EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["the academic value of Chinglish", "the creativity of the Chinese people", "the meaning of keeping Chinglish", "the creative combination of English and Chinese"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1805, "question": "D The year is 2094. It has been announced that a comet is heading towards the Earth . Most of it will miss our planet , but two pieces will probably hit the southern half of the Earth . On 17 July , a piece four kilometers wide enters the Earth's atmosphere with a massive explosion . About half of the piece is destroyed , but the remaining part hits the South Atlantic at 200 times the speed of sound . The sea boils and a huge hole is made in the sea bed . Huge waves are created and spread outwards from the hole . The wall of water , a kilometer high , rushes towards southern Africa at 800 kilometers an hour . Cities on the African coast are totally destroyed and millions of people re drowned . Before the waves reach South America , the second piece of the comet lands in Argentina . Earthqu...\n\nQ: Why can't the northern half of the earth escape for long ?", "options": ["Because the land is covered with water", "Because the light and heat from the sun can not reach the earth .", "Because people there can not live at the temperature of zero .", "Because wars break out among countries ."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3333, "question": "Japan Earthquake and Tsunami :How to Help For readers interested in contributing to help victims of the earthquake and tsunami that struck Japan and the Pacific region,here is a list of contact information and links for some agencies that plan to provide relief. THE JAPAN CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL EXCHANGE The Japan Center for International Exchange has set up the Japan NGO Earthquake Relief and Recovery Fund.Half of the money raised will go to support six Japanese NGOs currently at work in the disaster area and half will be retained to support the longer term recovery. AMERICAN RED CROSS Red Cross officials say donors can text REDCROSS to 90999 and a $10 donation will automatically be charged to donors' phone bill,or donations can be made directly on its Web site. B'NAI B'RITH INTERNATIONA...\n\nQ: If you want to make donations to the victims by phone,you can text REDCROSS to   _  .", "options": ["90999", "80888", "50555", "20006"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1971, "question": "Pets are popular. They're good listeners, they encourage us to exercise, and they're always on our side when we argue with others. They can bring people comfort and pleasure. But it is important to keep in mind that pets can carry diseases that can make you sick. Washing your hands often -- especially after you touch, feed, or clean up a pet -- is the best way to keep yourself healthy and prevent the spread of disease. Be sure to clean your fingernails carefully every time you wash. You also can protect your health by wearing gloves while cleaning animal cages or cat litter boxes. Avoid washing your pet in the bathtub , but if you do, always disinfect the tub immediately afterward. Be sure to bring your pet to the hospital for examinations every two weeks or month and whenever your pet is ...\n\nQ: To keep healthy, the author may be against   _  .", "options": ["washing your fingernails after touching your pet", "wearing gloves when cleaning your pet's cage", "washing your pet in the bathtub", "bringing your pet for examinations regularly"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2469, "question": "We human beings haven't been good friends to animals. For thousands of years, we have been polluting the environment, making it hard for animals to live on the planet. We have been killing animals for their fur, feathers or meat, or simply because they are dangerous. As a result, many kinds of animals have disappeared forever. Hundreds more are on the endangered list today. Should we care about animals? Of course we should. If animals of a certain kind all disappear, they will never come back again. Animals are more than just resources of things we need. Every kind of animal has its place in the balance of nature. Destroying any kind of animal can lead to many problems. For example, when farmers killed large numbers of hawks, the corn and grain that the farmers stored were destroyed by rat...\n\nQ: The example that farmers killed hawks shows that  _  .", "options": ["there were too many rats and mice", "hawks are the most important in the nature", "animals are good food resources", "every kind of animal is important in nature"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1359, "question": "A father with Parkinson's disease was arrested as he watched the Olympic cycling road race because he failed to smile or look as if he was enjoying himself. Mark Worsfold, a martial arts trainer and former soldier, claims that he was thrown to the floor and handcuffed just as cyclists passed by. His worried wife Nicola only found out he was being held after she reported him missing when he did not turn up for their daughter's ninth birthday party. The 54-year-old man had his fingerprints, DNA and _ taken before being questioned about why he did not appear to be enjoying the event on July 28. Police said Mr. Worsfold, who was held for over five hours, was arrested because of his manner, his state of dress and his being too near to the course. A spokesman added that the arrest was necessary ...\n\nQ: Which statement is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Worsfold's wife was immediately informed of his being arrested by the police.", "Worsfold was arrested because he was extremely dangerous.", "Worsfold enjoyed the cycle race though he saw it between the feet of people from the pavement.", "Worsfold was arrested because of his clothes as well as his facial expression."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3034, "question": "Are you a big fan of pirate stories? Do you know how to talk like a pirate? You can have fun on September 19th. This special holiday is called International Talk Like A Pirate Day. It was invented in 1995 by two young Americans, John Baur and Mark Summers. These two good friends came up with this idea when they were playing racquetball, and began to talk like pirates. At that moment, they thought, \"Young people are interested in pirate, but there is no such a chance for people to get together to share it. Why not have a day when everybody talks like a pirate?\" They decided to make September 19th the date. Since then, Baur and Summers have tried hard to promote Talk Like A Pirate Day. As Baur said, \"We've talked like pirates, and encouraged several of our friends to do so every September 19...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following can show that the holiday is special?", "options": ["It is a brand new holiday invented and celebrated by the youth themselves.", "It is a wonderful and instructive holiday.", "It has a long history.", "People can make their dream come true on this day."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2799, "question": "Any mistake made in the printing of a stamp raises its value to stamp collectors. A mistake on one inexpensive postage stamp has made the stamp worth a million and a half times its original value. The mistake was made more than a hundred years ago in the British colony of Mauritius, a small island in the Indian Ocean. In 1847 an order for stamps was sent to a London printer-Mauritius was to become the fourth country in the world to issue stamps. Before the order was filled and delivered, a ball was planned at Mauritius' Government House, and stamps were needed to send out the invitations. A local printer was instructed to copy the design for the stamps. He accidentally inscribed the words \"Post Office\" instead of \"Post Paid\" on the several hundred stamps that he printed. Today there are on...\n\nQ: Over a century ago, Mauritius   _  .", "options": ["was an independent country", "belonged to India", "was one of the British colonies", "was a small island in the Pacific Ocean"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3346, "question": "People with disabilities make up a large part of the population. It is estimated that over 35 million Americans have physical, mental, or other disabilities. About half of these disabilities are \"developmental\", i.e., they occur before the individual's twenty-second birthday, often from genetic conditions, and are severe enough to affect three or more areas of development, such as mobility, communication, employment, etc. Most other disabilities are considered \"adventitious\", i.e., accidental or caused by outside forces. Prior to the 20th century, only a small percentage of people with disabilities survived for long. Medical treatment for these disabilities was unavailable. Advancements in medicine and social services have created a climate in which people with disabilities can expect to h...\n\nQ: The best title for this passage might be   _  .", "options": ["Handicaps of People with Disabilities", "The physical difficulties of the Disabled", "The Causes for Disabilities", "Medical Treatments for Disabilities"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 417, "question": "For most of us, the rain that falls on our roof runs off into the ground or the sewer system. But if you want to save a little water and reuse it on your lawns or plants --- or even use it for laundry, dishes, or other needs --- collecting rainwater from your gutter's downspouts is a _ According to John C. Davis, writing in E / The Environmental Magazine, just about any homeowner can collect rainwater, given that the roof and gutters do most of the work. And since an inch of rain falling on a 2,000-square-foot roof produces some 1,200 gallons of water, you can harvest enough to water your lawn or garden. Plants and grass actually do better when fed rainwater instead of tap water, which is usually treated with substances that can hold back plant growth. Using rainwater can also extend the l...\n\nQ: What is the topic of the passage ?", "options": ["Basic gardening skills.", "Water-saving techniques.", "Wastewater treatment systems.", "Roof rainwater collection."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 532, "question": "A new study warns that about thirty percent of the world's people may not have enough water by the year 2025. An American organization called Population Action International did the new study. It was more than three hundred and thirty-five million people lack enough water now. The people live in twenty-eight countries. Most of the countries are in Africa or in the Middle East. Population Action International researcher Robert Engelman says by the year 2025, about three thousand million people lack water. At least 18 more countries are expected to have serious water problems. The demand for water keeps increasing. Yet the amount of water on the earth the same. Mr Engelman says the population in countries that lack water is growing in these countries will continue to increase. The report say...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["The amount of the water on earth will always stay the same.", "The report gives three solutions to water problem.", "M ost of the countries that lack water belong to the developing ones.", "There's only one long-term solution to solve the water problem, that is we must try our best to control the population growth."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 220, "question": "Do you find getting up in the morning so difficult that it's painful ? This might be called laziness, but Dr. Kleitman has a new explanation. He has proved that everyone has a daily energy cycle. During the hours when you labour through your work you may say that you're \"hot\". That's true. The time of day when you feel most energetic is when your cycle of body temperature is at its peak . For some people the peak comes during the forenoon. For others it comes in the afternoon or evening No one has discovered why this is so , but it leads to such familiar monologues as : \"Get up, John! You'll be late for work again !\" The possible explanation to the trouble is that John is at his temperature-and -energy peak in the evening. Much family quarrelling ends when husbands and wives realize what t...\n\nQ: The text is probably taken from a   _  .", "options": ["news report", "research paper", "medical textbook", "fashion journal"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1232, "question": "When your pet has an emergency, first aid is not a _ for veterinary treatment. However, before you are able to get your pet to a veterinarian , knowing some basic first aid can help. Bite Wounds Approach the pet carefully to avoid getting bitten. Wear a mask for the animal and then check the wound. Clean the wound with large amounts of saline . If these are not available, then regular water may be used. Wrap large open wounds to keep them clean. Bleeding Apply firm, direct pressure over the bleeding area until the bleeding stops. Hold the pressure for at least 10 minutes. Avoid bandages that cut off circulation. _ Check to see if the animal is choking on a foreign object. If an animal is not breathing, place it on a firm surface with its left side up. Check for a heartbeat. If you hear a h...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["doing pet first aid", "treating sick pets", "dealing with an emergency", "working as a veterinarian"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2991, "question": "Hidden in a small street in the south end of Springfield, not far from buildings torn apart by the tornado earlier this year, Frigo's is an Italian restaurant right in our own backyard. Frigo's is not a tiny place. It provides different kinds of Italian food. There are refrigerator cases full of prepared foods and desserts, and shelves filled with olives and various pasta. There's some traditional Italian music and the smell is of olive oil and garlic . Above the largest refrigerator case, there's a chalk board covered with desriptions of more Italian sandwiches than I could remember. I stepped into Frigo's almost by accident when I had to stay in Springfield into the evening for an open house at the school where I work. Frigo's is the perfect place to find something quick to go. There are...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that the writer  _  .", "options": ["seldom eats out in a restaurant with his family", "feels very happy that be has found Frigo's", "dislikes eating sandwiches", "lives a very relaxing life"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1076, "question": "What did you dream about last night? Did your teeth fall out or did you fly? Maybe you died or someone you know did.Or maybe you were back in high school.These are among the most common dreams people have and they all mean something.Here are some of the most common dreams and their interpretations or symbolism. Dreams of flying.Dreams of flying represent feelings of freedom that may result from an instance when you overcome a limitation or obstacle.Usually, children have more flying dreams than adults, because children are more open to their possibilities, and adults have often accepted limitations imposed by society. Teeth falling out.Food in a dream is symbolic of knowledge because food nourishes the physical body and knowledge nourishes the soul.Teeth are a means to break down food or k...\n\nQ: The text is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["high school dreams", "dreams' symbolism", "dreams of flying", "nightmares"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 636, "question": "As people have accurately observed,smiles are absent from early photographs. In 1852,for instance,a girl sat for her Daguerrotype,her head slightly turned,giving the camera an unsmiling look. She is preserved forever as a very serious girl indeed. Charles Darwin,a loving and playful parent,looks frozen in photographs. Why did our ancestors,from unknown sitters for family portraits to the great and famous,because so sad in front of the camera? The severity is everywhere in Victorian photographs. However,you don't have to look very long at these unsmiling old photos to see how incomplete the seemingly obvious answer is-that they are freezing their faces in order to keep still for the long exposure times. In Julia Margaret Cameron's Portrait of Tennyson,the poet dreams,his face a shadowed mas...\n\nQ: What do we know about the people in Victorian times?", "options": ["They laid importance on religious events.", "They were skillful at portrait painting.", "They valued their family life.", "They enjoyed themselves."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1965, "question": "Here is some general information about Edison Elementary School. For more information, you can visit our website which is printed on the cover. Attendance: Please contact the office at 480. 472. 5282 if your child is going to be absent. Renaissance Reading: The Accelerated Reader (AR) Program is a computerized reading enrichment program that combines great children's literature with computer skills. As an individualized reading program, it is designed to motivate students to read more and to read good literature. Students of different abilities can use this program. It is not a competitive program but one that improves any student's reading ability. Here is how it works. Students select books in their reading range from our Accelerated Reader Selection and read it at their own pace. Once t...\n\nQ: The passage is written for   _  .", "options": ["general readers", "parents", "teachers", "primary students"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 135, "question": "A 16-year-old South Dakota boy who became lost while hunting and spent 16 hours alone in the Black Hills National Forest says he was scared but still managed to make a survival plan. Austin DuVall, of Rapid City, became lost on Nov.3 while hunting with his father. He ran after a deer, and soon found himself alone. \"I ran after a deer, but I didn't get it,\" he said. \"Then I was really lost.\" He had only his hunting rifle and the clothes he was wearing. He had no food or water and had nothing that could help him find his way to safety. \"I knew that no one could hear me. I decided to just sleep and get up in the morning and find safety,\" he said. Austin climbed up on a rock and slept through the night. Then he awoke and relied on skills he learned in a hunter safety course. He followed a stre...\n\nQ: From what Mike Kintigh said, we learn that   _  .", "options": ["if someone gets lost in the Rocky Mountains, it is hard to find a way out", "too many people go missing in the Black Hills every year", "the rescue team is skillful enough to find the lost people in less than 24 hours", "people who are lost in the Black Hills have to spend a night in the woods"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2743, "question": "Occasionally, my father came back drunk. Late at night, he beat on the door, pleading to my mother to open it .He was on his way home from drinking, gambling, or some combination thereof, misspending money that we could have used and wasting time that we desperately needed. It was the late-1970s. My parents were separated. My mother was now raising a group of boys on her own. My father spouted off about what he planned to do for us, buy for us.In fact, he had no intention of doing anything. As a father who was supposed to love us, in fact, he lacked the understanding of what it truly meant to love a child--or to hurt one. To him, this was a harmless game that kept us excited and begging. In fact, it was a cruel, corrosive lie. I lost faith in his words and in him. I wanted to stop caring, ...\n\nQ: From the last parts (para7-11), we can infer that   _   .", "options": ["father liked to show off his family before others", "I couldn't understand Father's love unless he expressed to me", "father intended to show a loving father he was but failed.", "I would definitely treasure all the small love from father"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1603, "question": "Security Services advise that there have been robberies reported in the East Oxford area, carried out by a group and involving threats of and showing of a knife.The victims have all been young males of student age and appearance who have been walking alone between 7 pm and the early hours of the morning.Some of the victims have been followed from the O2 and the Regal Hotel. The Crime Prevention Advisor offers the following advice: *If possible walk home in a group, not on your own.If someone tries to take something from you by force, it may be best to give it to them, this way it will avoid you getting injured. *If someone tries to follow you, make for a public place, such as a shop or a restaurant or walk towards other people.Make lots of noise and use your personal alarm to shock the per...\n\nQ: What is mainly described in the text?", "options": ["A kind of security service.", "How to prevent the crime.", "How to fight for the crime.", "Safety on the streets at nights."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1327, "question": "City farms are gaining popularity in cities and towns around the United States. City Farms in Edmonston, Maryland, is located near shopping centers, car repair shops and homes. The neighborhood is a working-class community. People do not have very much money, and they have limited access to fresh food in markets. Over the past two years, the farm has attracted volunteers from the community like Marcy Clark. She schools her four children at home. On a recent day she brought them to Eco City Farms for a lesson. Alston Clark thinks his experience very valuable. \"I like coming out here, \"he says, \"You know, you connect with the earth, where your food comes from. You appreciate the food a little bit more. \" Margaret Morgan-Hubbard started Eco City Farms. She thinks of it as a place where people...\n\nQ: Eco City Farms have the following functions EXCEPT that    .", "options": ["they teach people how to have a sustainable community", "they improve the relationships between people in a community", "they demonstrate how to use green power in city life", "they help people learn to appreciate the food they have"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1292, "question": "You may think that light pollution isn't something extraordinarily important. You may believe that every other type of pollution has a larger impact on the environment than light pollution does. But light pollution is serious. Light pollution, or \"sky glow\", is the glow you can see at night above cities and towns. Light pollution is a problem that has been accompanying man ever since he started his first fire some 15,000 years ago. Light pollution is the light that comes from streetlights, buildings, parking lots and any other source of light that is reflected or directed into the atmosphere. Urban light pollution means that one-fifth of the world's population can no longer see the Milky Way with the naked eye . Many city kids, even if they did look through the orange smog above their head...\n\nQ: Beacuse of light pollution,the sea turtles hatchlings may  _", "options": ["find the sea easily", "cscape predaton", "be misled by bright lights from beachfront resorts", "find the way to the sea with the help of bright lights"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1060, "question": "In recent years many countries of the world have been faced with the problem of how to make their workers more productive. Some experts claim the answer is to make jobs more varied. But do more various jobs lead to greater productivity? There is evidence to suggest that while variety certainly makes the worker's life more enjoyable, it does not actually make him work harder. As far as increasing productivity is concerned, then variety is not an important factor. Other experts feel that giving the worker freedom to do his job in his own way is important, and there is no doubt that this is true. The problem is that this kind of freedom cannot easily be given in the modern factory with its complicated machinery which must be used in a fixed way. Thus while freedom of choice may be important, ...\n\nQ: The reason why a worker cannot have freedom in doing the job in his own way is that   _  .", "options": ["the machinery is so complex that it should be fixed", "the production lines are too large in modern factories", "the bosses can create very little freedom of choices for workers", "the machines must be operated strictly according to instructions and rules"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 104, "question": "The United States is full of cars. There are still many families without cars, but some families have two or more. However, cars are used for more than pleasure. They are a necessary part of life. Cars are used for business. They are driven to offices and factories by workers who have no other way to get to their jobs. When salesmen are sent to different parts of the city, they have to drive in order to carry their products. Farmers have to drive into the city in order to get supplies. Sometimes small children must be driven to school. In some cities school buses are used only when children live more than a mile away from the school. When the children are too young to walk too far, their mothers take turns driving them to school. One mother drives on Mondays taking her own children and the...\n\nQ: Mothers form car pools in order that  _  .", "options": ["they can drive to school", "they can take turns driving their children to school", "they reach school quickly", "they can drive their children to school in time"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1249, "question": "A woman wears a face mask to protect her from polluted air in prefix = st1 /Lanzhou,China, in December. A new study showed air pollution might put people more at risk for heart disease than scientists had thought. Kristin Miller, a doctoral student at the UniversityofWashington, said chances of getting the disease were related to not only which city a woman lived in, but also where in the city. The study found that the effects of air pollution were often larger within cities than between cities. The new findings make experts suspect that current pollution limits may be inadequate. Scientists examined rates of heart attack, stroke and other cardiovascular events in women with long-term exposure to air pollution. The study involved women over the age of fifty who had no sign of cardiovascula...\n\nQ: The case of the woman wearing a face mask shows   _  .", "options": ["people are paying more and more attention to their health", "the woman is afraid of getting heart disease", "Lanzhou city is more heavily polluted than other cities", "air pollution is becoming more and more serious"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 178, "question": "School education is very important and useful. Yet no one can learn everything from school. A teacher, no matter how much he knows, he can not teach his students everything they want to know. The teacher's job is to show his students how to learn. He teaches them how to read and how to think. So much more is to be learned outside school by the students themselves. It is always more important to know how to study by oneself than to learn some facts or a formula by heart. It is actually quite easy to learn a certain fact in history or a formula in mathematics. But it is very difficult to use a formula in working out a maths problem. Great scientist, such as Einstein, Newton and Galileo, didn't get everything from school. But they were all so successful and invented so many things for men. Th...\n\nQ: According to the passage, a good teacher should be one who is to  _  .", "options": ["help his students to gain a good memory.", "train his students' ability to learn", "teach his students everything he knows", "have his students studying long hours"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1073, "question": "Best places to visit in Australia Are you looking for the best places to see in Australia? Here are the top 5 places to visit in Australia. It includes the best, the most beautiful and the most famous. Sydney For those who have made a flight from the other side of the world, if you come and don't see Sydney, it is a bit like going to Germany and not drinking a beer, or to England and not seeing London, or America and not trying a hot dog. There is plenty to see and do in Sydney apart from the well known attractions of the Harbour Bridge, the Opera House, and Bondi beaches. Byron Bay Located in New South Wales, just south of the Queensland border, Byron Bay is popular with not just international tourists, but is also a favorite holiday destination of Australians. The lighthouse is amazing a...\n\nQ: What is the biggest problem when travelling in the Great Ocean Road?", "options": ["Its traffic problems.", "Its official length.", "You can't eat an America hot dog there.", "You must make a flight from the other side of the world."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2863, "question": "The sunflower plant bears bright yellow flowers that always face the sun, hence the name. However, the plant is grown not only for its beautiful flowers, but also for its oil that has a host of health benefits. Sunflower oil prevents diseases, lowers cholesterol levels, keeps the heart healthy, and even prevents certain forms of cancer. Sunflower oil is a kind of \"magic oil\" when it comes to skin care, as it makes your skin soft and smooth, and prevents signs of aging. So, let us know more about its effects on your skin. 1. It Acts as an Effective Emollient . Sunflower oil is an effective emollient, which means that it helps the skin retain moisture. Thus, people with dry skin can benefit immensely from the regular use of the oil. Also, it is mild, and provides relief from irritation and i...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Sunflower oil can weaken dark spots.", "Sunflower oil may lead to skin infections.", "Sunflower oil can make you attractive.", "Sunflower oil may keep eyes in comfort."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 264, "question": "Is It OK to Snap Your Food? Have you ever taken a snap of a luxurious cake or photographed a juicy steak when you eat in restaurants? You may want to share what you eat with your friends or just post part of your daily life onto the Internet. However, such action may be very annoying to other diners, or even to chefs and restaurant owners. Currently, more and more people begin to consider \" foodstagramming\" as very silly and a bad manner. In many restaurants, diners complain of being blinded by flasher , snapped without their permission and disturbed by people climbing on to chairs for a better angle. Even chefs and restaurant owners are annoyed at food photography. A Michelin-starred chef said, \"It's hard to build a memorable evening when flashes are flying every six minutes.\" At the star...\n\nQ: Which of the following is True?", "options": ["Customers in America like others to use flashes when they eat.", "Restaurants in Spain think of a methord to meet people's need.", "American government is discussing the problem of foodstagramming.", "People in China are trying to think of an idea to deal with the problem."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1074, "question": "Dutch treat is a late-nineteenth-century term, and it originally refers to a dinner where everyone is expected to pay for his own share of the food and drink. If people go \"Dutch treat\", or simply \"go Dutch\", it means that they will share the expenses of a social engagement. There are many other \"Dutch\" expressions in English, many of which were invented in Britain in the seventeenth century, when the Dutch and the English were commercial and military rivals. The British used \"Dutch\" to refer to something bad, cheap and shameful. A \"Dutch bargain\" at that time was an uneven, one-sided deal; \"Dutch reckoning\" was an unitemized account; and \"Dutch widow\" was slang for prostitute. Later centuries brought in \"Dutch courage\", for bravery caused by drink; \"Dutch concert\", for noisy music; \"Dutch...\n\nQ: Many of the \"Dutch\" expressions were invented with negative sense, because   _  .", "options": ["The Dutch were underdeveloped people.", "Britain and Holland were competitors at that time.", "The Dutch had many bad habits.", "The British were superior to the Dutch."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1944, "question": "Artie Shaw was born in New York City in 1910. His name was Arthur Arshawsky. His parents were poor immigrants who had come to the United States from Eastern Europe. His family later moved to New Haven, Connecticut. At the age of fourteen, he began to play the saxophone and then the clarinet. From a very young age, Artie Shaw wanted to play his clarinet better than anyone. He wanted his sound and music to be perfect. He worked at this task much of his life. He began working as a professional musician when he was fifteen. He left home and began playing in bands across the United States. In 1928, young Artie Shaw traveled to Chicago, Illinois to hear the great trumpet player, Louis Armstrong. He immediately understood that Armstrong's great jazz sound was the beginning of something new and ex...\n\nQ: When he was very young, Artie Shaw was    _   .", "options": ["born to a wealthy family", "a famous singer", "a man with a great dream", "was in love with music when he was a baby"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1916, "question": "Jack Benny was one of the most famous names in show business.He was born in Chicago,Illinois,on February 14th,1894.His parents,Meyer and Emma Kubelsky,were religious Jews.They had moved to the United States from Eastern Europe.Benny was a quiet boy.For much of the time,his parents were busy working in his father's store.As a child,Benny learned to play the violin.After finishing his school,he joined the Navy.He continued using his violin to perform for sailors.In one show he was chosen more for his funny jokes than for his skill with the violin.That experience made him believe that his future job was a comedian. Benny developed a show personality that had all the qualities people dislike.He was known for being so _ --he refused to spend any money unless forced to do so.On his shows Benny o...\n\nQ: According to the text,on Benny's shows,he   _  .", "options": ["developed a good personality", "played the violin skillfully", "often referred to his appearance", "said funny things that hurt others"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1624, "question": "On October 12, 1989, some Chinese scientists were working at the computers to look for information they needed. Suddenly they saw a lot of very bright spots crossing the computers's screens. At the same time the computers were working much slower. To find out what was happening they stopped their work to check some parts of the computers. To their horror, they found out that most of their stored information was got rid of by computer viruses ! Obviously all these computers had been infected by computer viruses. It is said that the computer viruses were made by a group of young men fond of playing tricks. They all had excellent education. They created the viruses just to show their intelligence . These kinds of computer viruses are named Jerusalem Viruses. These viruses can stay in computer...\n\nQ: According to the passage, computer viruses seem to  _  .", "options": ["have been in nature for years", "exist in any computers", "be difficult to get rid of at present", "be able to be got rid of in the near future"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 206, "question": "College is a fresh start, and a chance to make new friends. These friends may become your lifelong friends, or the person you want to spend the rest of your life with. Whether you are going to a nearby college or the university far away from home, you are likely to meet new people wherever you are. Here are some advice to help you make friends at college. Clearly, your classmates are all possible friends! Get to class early on the first day, and if you get there early enough, you will be in the room, or waiting outside it, with one other person, or a small group. A good casual opener would be to ask if you're in the right classroom, then introduce yourself, and explain that you're new, and a _ . Do this at all of your classes, and you will have a group of friends that you can make study gr...\n\nQ: Getting to class early will   _  .", "options": ["give you more information about the teacher", "let you concentrate more on your class", "give you a good chance to make friends", "leave a good impression on others"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 280, "question": "Chinese New Year celebrations, also known as the Spring Festival start on the 23rd day of the 12th lunar month of the Chinese calendar, and end on the 15th day of the first lunar month in the following year in the Chinese calendar. Chinese New Year's Day's date is calculated according to the Chinese lunar calendar. In 2015 it's Thursday, February 19. Many people clean their homes to welcome the Spring Festival. They put up the red posters with poetic verses on it to their doors, Chinese New Year pictures on their walls, and decorate their homes with red lanterns. It is also a time to reunite with s so many people visit their families at this time of the year. In the evening of the Spring Festival Eve, many people set off fireworks and firecrackers, hoping to cast away any bad luck and brin...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us", "options": ["Chinese New Year is around the corner", "what people usually do during Chinese New Year", "how people treat each other on the special day", "Chinese New Year witnesses the longest holidays"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 465, "question": "Teamwork is all about working together to achieve a common goal or purpose.Is teamwork out of date?Why it is so hard to effectively conduct teamwork in those things? One way we employ teamwork in everyday lives is by becoming a parent.It is a parent's job to teach their children the fundamental skills and give them the knowledge they need to be successful in life.So why is teamwork disappearing in this aspect of our lives?Well in today's society,we find that more and more parents are experiencing that the teamwork is one-sided thing.According to a 2009report from the US,there are 13.7million single parents raising their children in the US and this amount could be due to the fact that parents are not stepping up and taking responsibility for their children or they don't have the means to,so...\n\nQ: Teamwork is losing ground in workforce mainly because  .", "options": ["workers don't like to work together with others.", "workers'sense is affected by economic recession", "workers want to prove they are more capable", "fewer workers are employed to save money"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1857, "question": "A rainforest is an area covered by tall trees with the total high rainfall spreading quite equally through the year and the temperature rarely dipping below l6degC. Rainforests have a great effect on the world environment because they can take in heat from the sun and adjust the climate. Without the forest cover,these areas would reflect more heat into the atmosphere, warming the rest of the world. Losing the rainforests may also influence wind and rainfall patterns,potentially causing certain natural disasters all over the world. In the past hundred years,humans have begun destroying rainforests in search of three major resources : land for crops,wood for paper and other products,land for raising farm animals. This action affects the environment as a whole. For example,a lot of carbon dio...\n\nQ: What might be the best title for the text?", "options": ["How to Save Rainforests", "How to Protect Nature", "Rainforests and the Environment", "Rainforests and Medical Development"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2490, "question": "Actress Hayden Panettiere recently got into trouble with Japanese fishermen as she tried to stop them from killing dolphins. The 18-year-old star with some other surfers sailed out to reach the dolphins in order to stop them from being driven into a nearby pool and killed, but the six surfers, from Australia and the United States, were stopped by a fishing boat before they could reach them. The fishermen blocked their way with a boathook . It was an ugly, unfriendly and life-threatening struggle before the surfers were forced to return to the beach. It is believed that the dolphins were later taken into a pool and killed. Panettiere, who is a brave surfer and loyal animal protector, made up her mind to save the dolphins of Japan and said, \"It was really frightening. Some of us were hit by ...\n\nQ: Why did the surfers get into trouble with the fishermen in Japan?", "options": ["They said something that hurt the fishermen.", "They entered a pool which wasn't allowed to go into.", "They attacked Japanese culture.", "They tried to stop the fishermen from killing the dolphins."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2884, "question": "Skateboarding has become one of several non-traditional activities that PE teachers around America are introducing to inspire kids to exercise regularly. Some PE classes feature in-line skating, yoga, and even rock climbing. Experts have called those types of activities \"the new PE\". Such activities are part of a larger effort to help kids develop lifelong fitness habits and to keep them from becoming overweight. Now, 9 million U.S. children and teens are overweight. Obesity can lead to health problems such as diabetes and heart disease later in life. \"Our children and youth are becoming unhealthy and obese,\" says Johnson. \"Skateboarding is a great activity that keeps kids doing physical movement and gives them new skills and interest.\" Some schools don't allow skateboarding because they s...\n\nQ: Skateboarding is introduced into American schools to   _  .[", "options": ["encourage students to compete bravely in competition", "teach students how to deal with risk.", "prevent students suffering from heart disease later in life.", "help students form the habit of doing sports"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1335, "question": "Simona lives in Bucharest, Romania. She is nine years old and HIV positive . When Simona's mother found out about her illness five years ago, her first reaction was to tell everyone, looking for support. \"That's when I found out who really was my friend, and who wasn't, \"she said. \"Quite a few people stopped visiting me and asked their children not to play with Simona any more. Because of this, quarrels began in my family with each trouble brought about by her diagnosis. My husband became more and more unfriendly toward me and toward Simona. He didn't understand how important it was for Simona to receive regular examinations by a doctor or why she needed proper treatment for her sickness.\" When her mother tried to enroll Simona in a school, the teacher warned her that when other parents fo...\n\nQ: Simona's father thought that Simona   _   .", "options": ["shouldn't bring so much trouble to them", "should receive examinations regularly by a doctor", "shouldn't see the doctor for her sickness", "should be treated properly for her sickness"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 717, "question": "Alice's mother died when she was five. Although her brothers and sisters were loving and caring, their love couldn't take the place of a mother's. In 1925 Alice became my mother and told me that her family couldn't even afford her a doll. One afternoon in December 1982, when I was getting ready for Christmas, I suddenly decided to buy two dolls, one for my five-year-old daughter, Katie, and one for my old mother. Things went smoothly when a friend told me that his dad, who played Santa Claus in my area, would be willing to make a visit on Christmas morning to our home with the gifts! Knowing that my parents would also come to my house, I began to get ready for the most memorable day of my mother's life. Christmas Day arrived and so did Santa Claus at the planned time. Katie was very excite...\n\nQ: Why couldn't Alice get a doll as a child?", "options": ["Because her mother died quite early.", "Because her family disliked her.", "Because her family was very poor.", "Because Alice didn't love dolls."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 786, "question": "When Chinese student Du Juan brought her American boyfriend home two years ago to use the toilet, her Japanese roommate became so upset that she shouted in English: \"I hate you.\" Du, then 21 and an undergraduate at Bridgewater State College in Massachusetts, was shocked. So was her boyfriend. \"Later I realized that she didn't literally mean what she said and that she was not aware of the full meaning of the word 'hate' in English,\" said Du. \"It was more a problem with translation,\" she added. Cultural differences can cause confusion about what words or even actions mean, an issue that has come to the forefront recently following the arrest of a Chinese doctoral degree student in New Jersey. Zhai Tiantian, who studied at the Stevens Institute of Technology, has been accused of trying to set...\n\nQ: By saying \"It was more a problem with translation\", what does Du Juan mean?", "options": ["Translation was not the real problem, as Du Juan and her roommate can both speak English.", "Du Juan can not understand what her roommate meant at all.", "Her roommate didn't know what \"hate\" really meant in daily conservation.", "Her roommate spoke such poor English that she felt angry."], "answer": 2}]